sculptnouveau.com 2018-01-14

# Privacy Policy - Sculpt Nouveau

### Privacy Policy

#### Effective Date: June 15, 2016

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.sculptnouveau.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:

  * What information we collect.
  * With whom it is shared.
  * How it can be corrected.
  * How it is secured.
  * How policy changes will be communicated.
  * How to address concerns about personal data.

#### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services.

#### Your Access and Control of Information

You may opt out of any future contact from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change or correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

#### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon on your web browser or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

#### Notification of Changes

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. The updated Privacy Policy will be posted on our website with the date modified at the top of the document.

#### Orders

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and financial information (such as a credit card number and billing address). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

#### Cookies

This website may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

#### Do Not Track

This website does not track customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track signals.

Third parties that may have content embedded on our website, such as a social features, may set cookies on and/or obtain information about the fact that a web browser visited a specific website from a certain IP address. Third parties cannot collect any other personally identifiable information from this website unless you provide it to them directly. Your browser allows you to set the Do Not Track signal so that third parties know you do not want to be tracked.

#### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

#### Contact

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us via email or call 1-800-728-5787.
